omnicomgroup.com 2019-12-14

# Online Privacy Notice | Omnicom Group

Last updated: December 12, 2018

We at Omnicom Group Inc., along with Omnicom Management Inc., Omnicom Capital Inc. and Cardinia Real Estate LLC  (“collectively Omnicom”), respect your concerns about privacy.  This Online Privacy Notice applies to personal information we obtain through this website (“Site”). This Online Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we obtain through the Site, how we may use the information, with whom we may share it and the choices you may have regarding our use of the information.  We also describe the measures we take to safeguard the information and tell you how to contact us about our privacy practices.

Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:

  * Information We Obtain
  * How We Use The Information We Obtain
  * Information We Share
  * Your Options
  * Access and Correction
  * Data Transfers
  * Links To Other Websites
  * How We Protect Personal Information
  * Updates To Our Online Privacy Notice
  * How To Contact Us

Information We Obtain

We may obtain the following types of personal information when you choose to provide it through our Site:

  * Contact information, such as your name, postal address, email address and telephone number;
  * personal information in content you provide on our Site; and
  * information about your education, work and military history, legal work eligibility status, and other information relevant to specific jobs for which you may apply.

In addition, when you visit our Site, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies and web beacons.  The information we obtain in this manner includes IP address, browser characteristics, device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, information on actions taken on our site, and dates and times of website visits.  A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser.  A “web beacon,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server.  Through these automated collection methods, we obtain “clickstream data,” which is a log of content on which a visitor clicks while browsing a website.  As the visitor clicks through the website, a record of the action may be collected and stored.  Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies or how to restrict or disable certain types of cookies.  Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our Site.

Information about our cookie practices in the European Union is available here. To the extent required by applicable law, we will obtain your consent before collecting information using cookies or similar automated means.

How We Use The Information We Obtain

We use the information we obtain through the Site to:

  * respond to and communicate with you about your requests, questions and comments;
  * operate, evaluate and improve our business (including developing new products and services; managing our communications; determining the effectiveness of our sales, marketing and advertising; analyzing and enhancing our products, services and Site; and performing accounting, auditing, billing, reconciliation and collection activities); 
  * perform data analyses and other processing (including market and consumer research, trend analysis, financial analysis, anonymization, encryption and tokenization of personal information);
  * protect against, identify and prevent fraud and other criminal activity, claims and other liabilities; and
  * comply with and enforce applicable legal requirements, relevant industry standards and our policies.

In addition, we use information collected online through cookies, web beacons and other automated means for purposes such as (i) customizing our users’ visits to our Site, (ii) delivering content (including advertising) tailored to our users’ interests and the manner in which our users browse our Site, and (iii) managing our business.  We also use this information to help diagnose technical and service problems, administer our Site, identify users of our Site, and gather demographic information about our users.  We use clickstream data to determine how much time users spend on web pages of our Site, how users navigate through our Site, and how we may tailor our Site to better meet the needs of our users.  

We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

We may use third-party web analytics services on our Site, such as those of Google Analytics.  The analytics providers that administer these services use technologies such as cookies, web server logs and web beacons to help us analyze how visitors use the Site.  The information collected through these means (including IP address) is disclosed to these analytics providers, who use the information to evaluate use of the Site.  To learn more about Google Analytics and how to opt out, please visit  [www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

Our Site is not designed to respond to “do not track” signals received from browsers.

Information We Share

We do not sell or otherwise share personal information about you, except as described in this Online Privacy Notice.  We share personal information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.  These third parties are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements.  We also share the personal information we obtain with our affiliates and subsidiaries for the purposes described in the section of this Online Privacy Notice called “How We Use the information We Obtain.”

In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials based on a lawful disclosure request, or (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity.  We reserve the right to transfer any information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution or liquidation).

Your Options

We offer you certain choices about how we communicate with you and what information we collect from you.  To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists or submit a request, please contact us as indicated in the How To Contact Us section of this Online Privacy Notice.

Access and Corrections

To the extent provided by the law of your jurisdiction, you may (i) have the right to access certain personal information we maintain about you and obtain a copy of that information, (ii) update or correct inaccuracies in that information, (iii) object to our use of your personal information, and (iv) delete your personal information from our database.  To exercise these rights, please contact us as indicated in the How To Contact Us section of this Online Privacy Notice.  To help protect your privacy and maintain security, we may take steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the information.  A charge may be applicable before we provide you with a copy of any of your personal information that we maintain.

Data Transfers

Some of the personal information we collect about you through the Site will be transferred to countries other than the country in which the information originally was collected.  Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information.  When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Online Privacy Notice and will comply with applicable legal requirements.  

If you are located in the EEA or Switzerland, with respect to transfers of personal information to the U.S., Omnicom is certified under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield frameworks (collectively, the “Privacy Shield”) developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission and Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner, respectively, regarding the transfer of personal information from the EEA or Switzerland to the U.S.  Click here  \(EU:Swiss-US\).pdf")to view our EU/Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Privacy Policy.  

Links To Other Websites

Our Site may contain links to other websites for your convenience and information.  These websites may be operated by companies not affiliated with Omnicom.  Linked websites typically have their own privacy policies or notices, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites.  We are not responsible for the content of any websites that are not affiliated with Omnicom, any use of those websites, or the privacy practices of those websites.

How We Protect Personal Information

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.

Updates To Our Online Privacy Notice 

This Online Privacy Notice will be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices.  We will post a prominent notice on our Site to notify you of any significant changes to our Online Privacy Notice and indicate at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.

How To Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Online Privacy Notice, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us by email at [[privacy@omnicomgroup.com](mailto:privacy@omnicomgroup.com)] or write to us at:

_Omnicom Group Inc.  
Attn: General Counsel  
437 Madison Avenue  
New York, NY 10022_

If you are in the European Union, please contact:

_Omnicom Group Inc.  
Attn:Group Company Secretary  
239 Old Marylebone Road  
London, NW1 5QT  
United Kingdom_

%MCEPASTEBIN%
